globalmuonline.com 2007-06-22

# Official Global MU Online - Privacy Policy

Updated: May 10, 2007 

**K2 NETWORK PRIVACY POLICY**

**Protecting the privacy of all of our users and particularly children who may visit our site is an ongoing commitment of K2 Network, Inc. (hereinafter "K2 Network").**

K2 Network wants to provide for the safety and security of all of our members while using our website. Also included in this privacy policy are all other internet accessible services provided under the K2 Network name and marks. Our privacy policy has been created so that you are informed of the information K2 Network may gather about you when you visit our websites, how K2 Network may use this information, how and when we may disclose this information to others and how you can control the use of this information. You should be made aware of how you can modify or correct your information and how you can limit the disclosure of your personal information on the Internet. To accomplish this, K2 Network has established registration, sign-in procedures, and this Privacy Policy, to protect the privacy of information provided to K2 Network by its visitors and members while using the K2 Network website. 

Please take a few moments to read this agreement. By accessing the K2 Network website, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future as indicated below. 

  * What web sites and services are covered?
  * What information do we collect and who is collecting it?
  * What about cookies?
  * How do we use the information we collect?
  * Is the information secure?
  * How do I edit my personal information?
  * Do you share information with co-publishers of game developers?
  * Our Commitment to Children's Privacy.
  * Our Commitment to Data Security.
  * Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions.
  * Privacy of Information for the Merchant Center and Affiliate Center.
  * Contacting K2 Network.

**What web sites and services are covered by this Privacy Policy?**

We currently operate the following websites, game services and related game forums: 

From time to time, we may add new sites, game services and related forums that may not be listed above, but they will provide a link to this Policy and will be governed by its terms. 

**What information do we collect and who is collecting it?**

When you join a K2 Network website, game service or related forum, you are asked to provide limited personal identifier information to become a member. This type of information includes your name, home or other address, E-Mail addresses, telephone numbers or other information that tells another person about you. We also collect personal information from you in the event that you contribute information, data, text, software, artwork, character art, images, music, sounds, photographs, graphics, video, messages, or other materials (collectively, the "Content") to the K2 Network website, if for no other reason than to give you, the contributor, credit by name. We also collect information about each member's use of K2 Network's features and any survey responses or information regarding our users' interests and preferences. We want to make our policy regarding using this information very clear and concise. **K2 Network will not distribute, sell or rent any of the personal information you have provided to us without providing to you prior notice of our intention to do so and a clear opportunity for you to prevent any such disclosure**. Wherever possible, there will be a link to this privacy policy on every website page where personal information might be displayed or stored. You should also be aware that some websites that link to our site may also collect personal information about you (see "Cookies" section below). We cannot make any representations regarding the information privacy practices of those websites. You should also remember that any voluntary disclosure of personal information through E-Mail and in public-view uploaded materials can be seen and possibly used by others. Displaying personal information in such public fashion via our website or services may have unintended privacy implications for you. We encourage you to always remain aware of this possibility. In summary, K2 Network encourages you to use common sense and be cautious about what information you may provide on-line, whether through our websites or elsewhere on the Internet. With this approach and awareness, you can safely and enjoyably use and benefit from your Internet experience. 

**What about cookies?**

Cookies are used to store and track various types of information about K2 Network users. A cookie is a small piece of data that our web service sends to your browser and is stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies help us estimate the size of our audience. We use cookies to tell us what features of our website you visit most as well as what features on the site you do not visit. But again for your comfort, K2 Network never shares or provides any personal identifier information to any other party. 

**How do we use the information we collect?**

We have no hidden agenda regarding our use of your personal information. Our primary goal is to provide members with the most useful and enjoyable experience on the Internet. Unaffiliated third parties who license from us any Content you post on our website will never be privy to your personal user account information. Your E-Mail address may be used in order for us to send notices about new features, products, or other information that your personal information tells us might interest you, but we never share it with or provide it to others. You can choose to opt out of receiving these types of messages when you sign-on as a member, or at any later time. The K2 Network website is constantly evolving and changing in content and in features. Member-use information helps guide such changes and the evolution of our websites. The use of personal information in these ways allows us to provide a constantly evolving and user-sensitive package of services, products, and features that satisfy member needs, wants and desires but always with the priority of protecting individual member privacy. Every member should be aware that personal information may be legally and rightfully disclosed when it is required by law or when we are protecting K2 Network's rights or property or the rights or property of other K2 Network members, if we have reason to believe that other parties may be interfering with your or our rights and property. 

**Is the information secure?**

You are asked to choose a member ID and password when you join our website. Your password is known only to you unless you disclose it to others. We highly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. Also, if there are others who use your computer, you should always sign-out/log out of the K2 Network site and close your browser window when you are done using the Internet. Signing out/logging out helps protect your information if you are using a computer in a public place such as a library. At K2 Network, using the latest security hardware, software and operating procedures, we make every attempt to protect the privacy of your personal information stored in the K2 Network computer systems. However, in honesty you should be aware that there is no data that is transmitted over the Internet that can be guaranteed 100% secure in transmission or safe from theft or illegal acquisition. We will always do our best to protect against such occurrences. 

**How do I edit my personal information?**

All of your personal information is located in your personal K2 Network profile. Your profile can be edited at any time once you have signed in with your ID and password. Simply click on the "My Account" link and make your desired changes. 

**Do you share information with co-publishers of game developers?**

Certain K2 Network games may be provided to you in conjunction with a third party publisher or developer. A third party's use of the shared personal information will be governed by this Privacy Policy and K2 Network's use of such information shall, of course, be governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy. **Again, K2 Network will not distribute, sell or rent any of the personal information you have provided to us without providing to you prior notice of our intention to do so and a clear opportunity for you to prevent any such disclosure.**

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy.**

We at K2 Network take the online safety of children very seriously. The K2 Network website is designed and maintained for an audience at 18 years old and above. For this reason every member registration asks for date of birth and our best efforts are made to insure the integrity of our minimum age policy. 

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") requires that we inform parents and legal guardians about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information from children under 13 years of age. Although the K2 Network website is not directed at children under 13 years of age, we recognize that with proper adult supervision some parents might permit their children to visit and utilize the site. COPPA requires that we obtain the consent of parents and guardians in order for children under 13 years of age to use certain features of the K2 Network website. 

When your child attempts to register and/or provide personal information to K2 Network (including on the K2 Network website), we require a parent or legal guardian to: 

  * complete the registration;
  * review our privacy policy and to submit a valid credit card number to verify that the child's parent or guardian knows about and authorizes our information practices related to children protected by COPPA. 

Once parental notice and consent has been verified, the information we collect will be treated the same as information collected from any other user of the K2 Network website. Without verified parental notice and consent, we will not knowingly collect personal information of children under 13 years of age, and if we learn that we have inadvertently collected such information, we will promptly delete it. 

In compliance with COPPA, parents and legal guardians may request us to review, delete or stop the collection of the personally identifiable information of their child. You may do so in one of two ways. 

If you would like to review the information collected, please visit "My Account" after logging in, or you may contact us by letter or email using the address information provided at the bottom of this page. 

If you request that no further information about your child be collected or used, we will be required to terminate your child's ability to use the K2 Network webpages that require a user to "sign in." 

**Our commitment to data security.**

During sessions in which you give us information such as credit card numbers, we encrypt your transmissions using SSL ("Secure Sockets Layer") technology. We keep any personally identifiable information you provide us on servers that are protected by firewalls and other technological means against intrusion or unauthorized access. They are located in a physically secure facility, and only our employees and agents with a need to know the information are given access. While no amount of security can give a perfect guarantee, you can have a high degree of confidence that the personally identifiable information you give us is protected from unauthorized access and use. We rely on you to select passwords that cannot be easily guessed and to safeguard those passwords from disclosure. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions.**

We will notify our members, by E-Mail or by posting a notice on our website, when we make any significant changes to our Privacy Policy that affect the use of any personally identifiable information we collect. Your continued use of our website will constitute acceptance of the changes and the existing privacy policy. In instances where we ask for your personally identifiable information and we tell you the data we are collecting on that page will be shared with unaffiliated third parties, and in cases where a member of the K2 Network community opts-in to share his/her information with third parties, those disclosures and opt-ins will override anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy. In addition, K2 Network reserves the right to make non-significant changes to our Privacy Policy that will not affect K2 Network's use of a user's personally identifiable information at any time without any notice to you other than posting any such changes in a revised Privacy Policy on the K2 Network website. We encourage you to periodically review our Privacy Policy to be sure you are familiar with the most current version. The Policy will include the most recent date in which any revision has been made. Please note that this Privacy Policy is also incorporated, by reference, into K2 Network's Terms of Use. 

**Privacy of Information for the Merchant Center and Affiliate Center**

K2 Network is committed to the privacy of information collected by these programs as much as it is committed to the privacy of information related to game customers. The policies in this document apply to both the Merchant Center and Affiliate Center. We may request additional information to confirm the identity of you, your banking institution, or your business. To further protect you, we may also have additional confirmatory requirements for changing your information stored at the Merchant Center and Affiliate Center.

**Contacting K2 Network.**

If you have a privacy concern regarding the K2 Network website or this policy, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of the website, you can write to us by email at [privacy@k2network.net](mailto:privacy@k2network.net). Alternatively, we can be reached by our postal mail address: 

K2 Network, Inc.  
14252 Culver Dr. #A355  
Irvine, 92604  
Attention: Director, Privacy 

If you object to any sharing of your personal information that may be permitted under this policy, you may do so by writing us at the above address. We will take reasonable steps to accommodate your requests as they relate to our commercial practices. In some instances, honoring your requests may interfere with or preclude your ability to use the K2 Network website or may require us to terminate our relationship with you.
